There Are Moments That Test Us And Choices That Define Us
The Yellow Birds is a war, drama film directed by Alexandre Moors.
Two young soldiers, Bartle and Murph, navigate the terrors of the Iraq war
under the command of the older, troubled Sergeant Sterling.
All the while, Bartle is tortured by a promise he made to
Murph's mother before their deployment.
Daniel Murphy, played by Tye Sheridan.
Brandon Bartle, played by Alden Ehrenreich.
Maureen Murphy, played by Jennifer Aniston.
Sergeant Sterling, played by Jack Huston.
Captain Anderson, played by Jason Patric.
Amy Bartle, played by Toni Collette.
The Yellow Birds is a 2017 American war film directed by Alexandre Moors
and based on the novel The Yellow Birds by Kevin Powers.
The film stars Tye Sheridan, Alden Ehrenreich, Toni Collette,
Jason Patric, Jack Huston, and Jennifer Aniston.
The story is about two young U.S.
soldiers who navigate the terrors of the Iraq War.
When only one of the soldiers returns home, he is tortured by a promise
he made to the other's mother before their deployment.
The film had its world premiere at the Sundance
Film Festival on January 21, 2017.
It was released on May 17, 2018, through DirecTV Cinema before being released in a
limited release and through video on demand on June 15, 2018, by Saban Films.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book, soldier, iraq war, virginia.
The tone is emotional.